invoicehome.com 2018-12-27

# Privacy Policy - Invoice Home

This Privacy Policy applies to all of the websites, Services (referred to collectively as the ‘Services’ or ‘Service’ in this document ) and products offered by Wikilane Inc. (‘Wikilane’) or its subsidiaries or affiliated companies.

This Privacy Policy applies to Wikilane Services only. Some pages of our websites may contain external links. You should verify the privacy practices of such websites; third party application providers are governed by their own privacy policies.

## Personal & Financial Information

We understand your need for online privacy and therefore take the appropriate measures to protect any personal or financial information you may share with us.

When you create a user account, we may ask for your name, company name, billing address and email address. If you sign up for Services requiring payment, we may ask for your credit card or other payment account information.

The information you provide will be used mainly for the purpose of identification and authentication, billing, products and Services provisions, improvement, and research. We may combine this information with information from other Wikilane or third party services in order to improve the quality of our Services and to provide you with a better user experience.

Within the context of providing the Service and for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf, we may need to disclose Personal Information to our affiliates, service providers and other trusted business partners.

Wikilane processes personal information on servers and cloud services in the United States of America and in other countries. Therefore, in some cases, we may process your personal information outside your own country.

The information you provide is not sold or shared to others except to provide products or Services you’ve requested or when we have your permission.

We may also disclose information you provide to prevent, investigate, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats, and violations of Wikilane terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

## Security

We care about your personal information. Sensitive information, such as credit card numbers, are encrypted by using secure socket layer technology (SSL). We use industry standards to protect personal information, but you should be aware that no method of transmission over the Internet, or data storage, is 100% secure. We make our best efforts to protect your personal information, but we cannot guarantee its ultimate security.

## Data Storage

Wikilane makes no claim to the rights of your data, but Wikilane owns the databases and all rights to our applications.

## Cookies, Server Logs

To enhance the user’s experience and to improve the quality of our Services and tracking user trends we use temporary and permanent cookies or pixel tags which may include an anonymous unique identifier. If you have turned cookies off, you may not be able to use some Wikilane Services. Our cookies will elapse after a certain period of time to protect you against unauthorized access to the content of your account.

When you access Wikilane Services via a browser, our servers may record certain information such as your interaction with a Service, requests, IP address, browser type, language, and cookies that may uniquely identify your account and browser.

## Changes to Privacy Policy

Wikilane reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy Statement at any time. Any Privacy policy Statement changes will be published on our website, so please review it periodically.

If Wikilane becomes involved in an acquisition, merger, or any form of sale, notice will be published on our website before your personal information becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy Statement, please contact us at [legal@wikilane.com](mailto:legal@wikilane.com)
